

Address
Dimitrija Avramovića 13
21000 Novi Sad
Phone
+38167 720 1771
Email
filipeng97@gmail.com
LinkedIn

Languages
English B2
German A1

Github

Skills
JavaScript
Node.js
React.js
Next.js
MongoDB
MySql
PostgreSQL
RabbitMQ
AWS

Other skils
Java (Spring)
C, C++, C#
Php
WordPress
Angular
Vue.js
Python
Keras

FILIP MLADENOVIĆ

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

About —

Ever since I was a little kid, software development has been my passion. I still remember sitting in front of a Windows XP machine, with the QBASIC command panel printing "Hello World" for the very first time. This passion introduced me to the Web Development world where I've met true artists. Web applications are more than a piece of art because their purpose is not only to be beautiful, but useful as well. I am a fan of Breaking Bad and my motto is "Be the one who knocks!" - Take responsibility and improve yourself.

Education

20/10/2020 - 29/09/2021 - Novi Sad, Serbia

Master of Software Engineering - Faculty of Techical Sciences

01/10/2016 - 16/09/2020 - Novi Sad, Serbia

Software engineering and techical science - Faculty of Techical Sciences

■ Work Experience ■

01/10/2021 - Present - Freelance

Software Engineer – Daytrip

Technology stack: Node.js, React.js, MongoDB, AWS

01/04/2019 - 01/10/2021 - Freelance

Team Lead - Software Engineering Institute

Technology stack: React.js

01/09/2020 - 01/10/2021 - Novi Sad, Serbia

Software Engineer - Ex Nihilo

Technology stack: React.js, Node.js, MongoDB, MySql, AWS

Projects

BeeYou

- This is a meeting based platform where you can live stream videos.
- I have worked on features implementation. One of the key features that I have implemented was an innoviative payment process for live streams.
- Architecture were devided into three major parts: Backend (Node.js, MongoDB), frontend (React.js with provider context), and microservice based on socket.io. Deployed on AWS.
- Link: https://beeyou.tv/

Remotely

- Platform for job searching (posting).
- I have had the assignment to refactor one part of the platform which is dedicated to jobs and applicants management.
- Technologies: serverless node (aws lambdas), next.js for server side rendering with Cloadflare cache, and PostgreSQL database.
- Links: https://jsremotely.com/, https://phpremotely.com/

Daytrip

- Platform for trip booking.
- I have worked on feature improvement and implementation, testing, and deploying.
- Technologies: node.js, react.js, next.js, mongodb, AWS
- Link: https://mydaytrip.com/